{
    "subject": "resource/Sitmar_Cruises",
    "predicate": "ontology/service",
    "object": "resource/Cruise_ship",
    "human_readable": "Sitmar Cruises offers a service related to Cruise ship.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.947849452495575,
            "question": "What kind of service does Sitmar Cruises offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8539993762969971,
            "question": "What are some popular destinations offered by Sitmar Cruises?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.842583179473877,
            "question": "What amenities or features are commonly found on Sitmar Cruises' ships?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.825846791267395,
            "question": "What type of transportation does Sitmar Cruises provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.820038914680481,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of Sitmar Cruises' services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8074440956115723,
            "question": "Are there any special promotions or deals offered by Sitmar Cruises?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7918692231178284,
            "question": "Does Sitmar Cruises cater to specific types of travelers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7547861933708191,
            "question": "Can you describe what a Sitmar Cruises experience typically involves?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6785029768943787,
            "question": "How can someone book a cruise with Sitmar Cruises?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593636274337769,
            "question": "What makes Sitmar Cruises unique compared to other cruise lines?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sitmar Cruises offers a service related to Cruise ship.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7097_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How can someone book a cruise with Sitmar Cruises?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7097_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe what a Sitmar Cruises experience typically involves?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7097_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Sitmar Cruises cater to specific types of travelers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7097_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7097_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sitmar Cruises offering cruise services, which supports the statement that \"Sitmar Cruises offers a service related to Cruise ship.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}